gianttiger.ca 2017-06-11

# Privacy Policy | Giant Tiger

Last updated: September 9, 2014

Giant Tiger Stores Limited (“ **Giant Tiger** ”) is committed to protecting your privacy and safeguarding your personal information. This includes all personal information acquired through our contests, surveys and/or promotions or through interactions with our websites. This privacy policy will outline how we collect, use and retain your personal information.

##  **Your Consent to This Privacy Policy**

**BY SUBMITTING PERSONAL INFORMATION TO GIANT TIGER OR OUR RESPECTIVE SERVICE PROVIDERS OR AGENTS VIA OUR WEBSITE, IN OUR RETAIL STORES, YOU CONSENT TO OUR COLLECTION, USE AND DISCLOSE OF SUCH PERSONAL INFORMATION FOR THE PURPOSES DESCRIBED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY, AND/OR FOR PURPOSES STIPULATED AT TIME OF COLLECTION AND AS PERMITTED OR REQUIRED BY LAW.** Subject to legal and contractual requirements, you may opt out of receiving communications from our email club by setting your email preferences to opt-out or by clicking on the unsubscribe link in our emails. Your personal information may be retained in the database to ensure that we honour your privacy requests to opt-out of certain communications, for record keeping purposes, for internal research and analysis, and the other purposes described in this Privacy Policy. If you provide us with personal information concerning another individual, you represent and warrant that you have all necessary authority and/or have obtained all necessary consents from such individual to enable us to collect, use and disclose such personal information for the purposes set forth in this Privacy Policy.

##  **Personal Information**

Personal information may include, but not be limited to, your name, address, telephone number, or  email address. You may happen to provide us with such information through resources such as regular mail, our on-line application form or via our email addresses. In all cases, we will take steps to ensure that the information is handled securely. These steps are taken in order to comply with legislative requirements of applicable privacy laws. Personal information does not include aggregated information that does not allow an individual to be identified.

##  **Collecting, Using and Protecting your Information**

We collect, use and disclose personal information in accordance with applicable privacy and data protection laws and regulations. Giant Tiger collects personal information (including, without limitation, names, addresses, telephone numbers and email addresses) that you provide when you (a)  sign up to join our email club; (b) participate in a contest or sweepstakes promotion; (c) sign up for and/or fill out a survey or questionnaire; (d) apply for an employment opportunity; (e) contact Giant Tiger by email or otherwise, this includes a customer service representative. 

Information is only collected with your consent, and will be used for the sole purpose that is stipulated at the time the information is gathered. Your consent is deemed to be given when you send information to us through the internet. Giant Tiger does not sell or share customer information with any other organization or person for any reason. 

The information sent to Giant Tiger is kept confidential and secure. We make every reasonable effort to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of personal information under our control. We operate secure data networks protected by industry standard firewall and password protection systems. Our security policies are reviewed and enhanced as necessary.

Only authorized employees and providers have access to your personal information. Where information is processed by a third party provider, we make sure, through our contracts with them, that all your information is kept secure. Our service providers may be located outside of Canada and may be required to disclose personal information under the laws of their jurisdiction. Information is only kept for the duration we are providing you with a product or service and for a reasonable time thereafter in the event that you wish to resume service. 

Examples of how we use your personal information include:

**Product and Service Fulfillment**

  * Fulfill and manage purchases, orders, payments, returns/exchanges, or requests for information, or to otherwise serve you 

**Marketing Purposes**

  * Deliver coupons, promotions, sweepstakes, contests, newsletters, regular flyers, emails, as well as mobile coupons and messages you have chosen to receive
  * Send marketing communications and other information you have chosen to receive regarding products, services and promotions
  * Administer promotions
  * Administer sweepstakes and contests 

**Internal Operations**

  * Improve the effectiveness of our website, stores, mobile experience and marketing efforts
  * Conduct research and analysis, including focus groups and surveys
  * Perform other internal business activities as needed, or as described elsewhere in this policy

**Fraud Prevention**

  * To prevent fraudulent transactions, monitor against theft and otherwise protect our guests and our business 

**Legal Compliance**

  * To assist law enforcement and respond to subpoenas, search warrants, or other legal/regulatory orders or inquiries

## **Accuracy of Personal Information**

For the most part, we collect personal information that is directly supplied by you. We will therefore assume the information you have provided us with is accurate. We will not make additional efforts to verify its accuracy or to update the information unless requested by you. Customers and/or applicants may request in writing access to their personal information; to do so please write to the address indicated below. Any information we have on record will be provided to you. You may at that time put in a request for your information to be updated to ensure its accuracy.

##  **Non-Personal Information Collected Automatically**

We do not require your personal information in order for you to access this website. We may collect information about you that is not personally identifiable such as the type of internet browser or computer operating system you are using and the domain name of the website from which you linked to our site. In addition, when you view our websites, we may store some information on your computer in the form of a "cookie" or similar file. Cookies allow us to tailor a website or promotion to better match your interests and preferences. Most Internet browsers enable you to erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. Please refer to your browser instructions or help screen to learn more about these functions. Giant Tiger does not collect your personal information automatically, but we may tie the information that we do collect automatically (such as the type of internet browser that you use) to your previously submitted personal information.

Giant Tiger allows service providers and third-party companies to collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit our websites and to use that information to serve ads for Giant Tiger products or services or other companies’ products or services when you visit gianttiger.com or other websites. The information (e.g., clickstream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) is used during your visits to Giant Tiger’s websites and other websites to provide advertisements about products and services that also may be of interest to you. These parties typically use a cookie or a web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioural advertising practice or to manage your choices ( e.g., opt in or opt out) for this type of advertising, you can visit the Interactive Advertising Bureau of Canada (IAB Canada) website ( _<http://iabcanada.com/>_ ).

If you would like to  opt out of Google collecting your browsing history, please download their browser add-on here: _<https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/>_

## **Passwords**

You are responsible for the security of your account and password. Giant Tiger will not be liable for any losses, damages or expenses arising out of or relating to any unauthorized use of such account or password.

##  **Credit Card Security**

We value your security and privacy with all online transactions. We use Secure Sockets Layer (“ **SSL** ”) technology to protect the security of your credit card information as it is transmitted to us. 

SSL is the industry standard for secure commerce transactions. It prevents your personal information from being read by someone else as it travels across the Internet. All of your personal information is encrypted, including credit card number, name and address. **While we implement the above security measures on this  website, you should be aware that 100% security is not always possible.**

## **Information from Other Sources**

We may also obtain information from other sources that help us analyze, update, expand our records and identify new guests ( e. g., updating contact information or adding demographic information). Giant Tiger uses the information to improve our ability to contact you and increase the relevance of our marketing to you. These companies must follow privacy laws when collecting and sharing the information with Giant Tiger.

##  **Links to Other Websites**

Our website may contain links to other websites, including content from other websites that is occasionally framed within the Giant Tiger’s  site. Please note that the privacy policies applicable to the collection of personal information on those other websites may be different from this one and we have no control or responsibility for the privacy practices of third party websites. You are advised to review the privacy policy of any website linked to or framed within the Giant Tiger’s site prior to providing any personal information.

##  **Social Plug-Ins**

We have installed on our  website various social media plug-in protocols, such as a Facebook “Like” button, which allow you to share your likes and interests in Giant Tiger’s products, services and promotions with your friends and contacts. When you click on a social media plug-in protocol link, such as the “Like” button, a link to our site may appear in the “Likes and Interests” section of your Facebook or other social media profiles. Your friends and contacts will be able to see the link and be led back to our  site if they share your likes and interests or if they are interested in learning more about our products, services and promotions. By using a social media plug-in protocol link, you consent to receiving communications from us for all of these purposes and agree to allow us to use information on your likes and interests in connection with the marketing and promotion of our business. For more information about social media plug-in protocols, such as the Facebook “Like” button and its impact on your privacy rights, please visit the appropriate social media help center ( e. g., Facebook’s Help Center at _<https://www.facebook.com/help/340599879348142/>)._

## **Privacy Policy Revisions**

We may change or add to this Privacy Policy from time to time, so we encourage you to review it periodically. Revisions may reflect changes in how we collect, use, share and protect your personal information, as well as changes in our legal or regulatory obligations. The Privacy Policy posted on www.gianttiger.com is the one currently in effect. To help you keep track, we include the date of our most recent updates.

##  **Contacting our Privacy Officer**

If you have any questions or concerns, or should you wish to access or update your information, you can write to:

**Giant Tiger Stores Limited**  
Privacy Officer   
2480 Walkley Road   
Ottawa, Ontario   
K1G 6A9
